Guide to the Beecher Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1806-1818, 1822-1849, (1850-1930), 1931-1948, 1964; Series I; 19' (46 boxes)
  - Beecher-Scoville Family Correspondence
    - Beecher Family
      - Beecher, Jessie Howe (Bigelow)
        - Beach, Ella, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
      - Beecher, Lyman
        - To L.B.:
          - Beecher, Edward (Box 1, Folder 57)
          - Parker, Rev. Joel, 1852 (Box 1, Folder 58)
        - From L. B.:
          - Beecher, [a son], 1850 (Box 2, Folder 59)
          - Brainerd, Rev. Thomas, 1836-1940 (Box 2, Folder 60)
          - Foote, George Augustus, 1818-1929 (Box 2, Folder 61)
          - Goodrich, Rev. Chauncey Hopkins, [Henry], 1828, 1842 (Box 2, Folder 62)
          - Nettleton, Rev. Asahel., 1827 (Box 2, Folder 63)
            See also: Box 2, Folder 62
          - Tappan, Lewis, 1828 (Box 2, Folder 64)
          - Taylor, Rev. Nathaniel William, 1816 (Box 2, Folder 65)
          - Unidentified, re: sermon, 1827 (Box 2, Folder 66)
          - Circular letter on behalf of Lane Seminary, 1851 (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Beecher, Martha L.
        - Peck, Maria, April 22, 1832 (Box 2, Folder 68)
        - Mayhew, C. L. to Beecher, M., February 22 (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Beecher, Patty [Mrs. Lewis]
        - Judel, Ulrich P., February 1834 (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - Beecher, Roxana (Foote)
        - Foote, George Augustus, 1809 (Box 2, Folder 71)
        - Foote, Harriet, 1806-1813 (Box 2, Folder 72)
      - Beecher, William Constantine
        - To W. C. B.:
          - Beecher, Charles, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 73)
          - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard), 1871-1883, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 74-75)
          - Cruikshank, Alfred B., 1927 (Box 2, Folder 76)
          - Dunlap, J. M., 1887 (Box 2, Folder 77)
          - Ellinwood, T. J., 1887 (Box 2, Folder 78)
          - Emery, S. Hopkins, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 79)
          - Hall, Rev. Charles H., 1888 (Box 2, Folder 80)
          - Hertz, Emanuel, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 81)
          - Johnson, Oliver, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 82)
          - Mears, Mary G. (Mrs. David O.), 1887 (Box 2, Folder 83)
          - Moores, Julia Merrill (fragment), undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
          - Northrup, Bertha West, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 85)
          - Plymouth Church Board of Trustees, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 86)
          - Scoville, Harriet E. B., 1873-1900 (Box 2, Folder 87)
          - Scoville, Rev. Samuel, 1873 (Box 2, Folder 88)
          - Stowe, Charles Edward, [1927] (Box 2, Folder 89)
          - Tappan, Lewis W., 1887 (Box 2, Folder 90)
          - Tower, [Jennie M.], 1927 (Box 2, Folder 91)
          - Wright, Rev. William Burnet, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 92)
          - Unidentified, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 93)
        - From W. C. B.:
          - [Beach], Ella, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 94)
          - [Beach], Emma, 1868 (Box 2, Folder 95)
          - Gunn, Frederick William, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 96)
          - Johnson, [Oliver], 1878 (Box 2, Folder 97)
          - New York, 1879 (Box 2, Folder 98)
          - Storrs, Rev. Richard Salter (Box 2, Folder 99)
          - Fragment, undated (Box 2, Folder 100)
      - Beecher, William Henry., July 29, 1837 (Box 2, Folder 101)
      - Burton, Mary Beecher (Hooker)
        - Unidentified, 1871 (Box 2, Folder 102)
      - Hooker, Isabella Homes(Beecher)
        - To Connecticut General Assembly, 1822-1907, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
      - Hooker, John
        - Seeley, R. H., 1875 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      - Perkins, Mary Foote (Beecher)
        - Beecher, Catherine Esther, 1851 (Box 2, Folder 105)
        - Stowe, Harriet Elisabeth (Beecher), 1881 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Eunice White (Bullard) Beecher
      - To E. W. B.:
        - Abbott, Emma, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 108)
          (107 not assigned)
        - Abbott, Rev. Lyman, 1891-1892 (Box 3, Folder 109)
        - Anderson, John, 1884-1888 (Box 3, Folder 110)
        - Barnes, Will, 1881 (Box 3, Folder 111)
        - Barton, Anna M, 1874 (Box 3, Folder 112)
        - Barton, W. S., 1850 (Box 3, Folder 113)
        - Beecher, Catherine Esther, (1800-1878), 1851 (Box 3, Folder 114)
        - Beecher, Charles, 1895-1897 (Box 3, Folder 115)
        - Beecher, Edward, (1803-1895), 1880 March (Box 3, Folder 116)
        - Beecher, Esther M. (1799-1855), 1848-1855, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
        - Beecher, Harriet Jones (Benedict), 1863 1895 (Box 3, Folder 118)
        - Beecher, Henry Barton, (1841-), 1861-1872, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
        - Beecher, Henry Ward (Box 3, Folder 120)
          See: Boxes 7-8, Folders 308-321
        - Beecher, Herbert Foote, (1854-1925), 1868-1873, 1872 October-1873 May (Box 3, Folder 121-124)
        - Beecher, Herbert, (1854 Aug-1925), 1873 August-1874, undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
        - Beecher, Rev. James Chaplin, (1828-1886), 1861 (Box 3, Folder 126)
        - Beecher, Jessie Howe (Bigelow), undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
        - Beecher, Lydia (Beals) Jackson, 1851 (Box 3, Folder 128)
        - Beecher Memorial Church, Brooklyn, 1892 (Box 3, Folder 129)
        - Bok, Edward William, (1863-1930), 1886-1887 Mar, 1887 July-1888, 1893-1896, undated (Box 3, Folder 130-133)
        - Bok, William J., undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
        - Bonner, Robert, (1824-1899), 1866-1867 (Box 3, Folder 135)
        - Bronson, Annie H., 1867-1868 (Box 3, Folder 136)
        - Bullard, Jane, 1865 (Box 3, Folder 137)
        - Bullard, Katherine, 1895 (Box 3, Folder 138)
        - Bullard, Lucy W., 1857-1859 (Box 3, Folder 139)
        - Chadwick, John W., 1887 (Box 3, Folder 140)
        - Chaplin, Frances P., 1869-1870 (Box 3, Folder 141)
        - Chaplin, Jane Dunbar, 1868-1869 (Box 3, Folder 142)
        - Charles Scribner and Co., [1869] (Box 3, Folder 143)
        - Cleveland, Frances (Folsom) (1864-1947), 1888 (Box 3, Folder 144)
        - Cleveland, Stephen Grover (Pres.) (1837-1908), 1887 (Box 3, Folder 145)
        - Conant, Esther Church, 1875 (Box 3, Folder 146)
        - Congregational Church and Society of New Lisbon, Wisconsin, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 147)
        - Connell, Jennie, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 148)
        - Corning, J. L., 1887 (Box 3, Folder 149)
        - Cowles, Sarah B., [1869] (Box 3, Folder 150)
        - Curtis, George William, 1869 (Box 3, Folder 151)
        - Curtis, Mary Louise, [1896] (Box 3, Folder 152)
        - Day, Clinton, 1878 (Box 3, Folder 153)
        - Day, Roger S., 1874 (Box 3, Folder 154)
        - Derby, James Cephas, 1880-1884 (Box 3, Folder 155)
        - Dewey, Samuel, 1875 (Box 3, Folder 156)
        - Dunning, A. K., 1868-1869 (Box 3, Folder 157)
        - Dunning, E. D., 1869 (Box 3, Folder 158)
        - Fisk, Clinton Bowen, (1828-1890), 1875 (Box 3, Folder 159)
        - Fisk Jubilee Singers, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 160)
        - Free Methodist Church Brisbane, Australia, 1887 (Box 3, Folder 161)
        - Garfield, Lucretia (Rudolph) (1832-1918), 1887 (Box 3, Folder 162)
        - Gibson, Elizabeth T., 1874 (Box 3, Folder 163)
        - Glen, F. W., 1875 (Box 3, Folder 164)
        - Green, Julia W., 1875 (Box 3, Folder 165)
        - Gunn, Frederick William (1816-1881), 1876 (Box 3, Folder 166)
        - Hale, Sarah Josepha, 1869 (Box 4, Folder 167)
        - Harper and Brothers, 1869 (Box 4, Folder 168)
        - Hart, Thomas Carlyle, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 169)
        - Hawley, Harriet W., 1874 (Box 4, Folder 170)
        - Henry, Mrs., [c.1875] (Box 4, Folder 171)
        - Hickok, H. T., 1876 (Box 4, Folder 172)
        - Hinsdale, Grace W., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 173)
        - Holbron, T. V., 1883 (Box 4, Folder 174)
        - Hosford, T. J., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 175)
        - Howard, Oliver Otis, (1830-1909), 1894 (Box 4, Folder 176)
        - Howard, Susan Taylor (Raymond) (d. 1906), 1857-1888, undated (Box 4, Folder 177)
        - Johnson, M. O., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 178)
        - Johnson, Sophie Orne, 1868-1869 (Box 4, Folder 179)
        - Johnston, J. H., 1883 (Box 4, Folder 180)
        - Kimball, Edward, 1877 (Box 4, Folder 181)
        - Kranskope, Rabbi Joseph, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 182)
        - Ludlow, Frances A., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 183)
        - McLean, Samuel, undated (Box 4, Folder 184)
        - McLeod, Peter, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 185)
        - Maxwell, Mrs. Abbie, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 186)
        - Myers, A. M., 1875 (Box 4, Folder 187)
        - New York, 1869 (Box 4, Folder 188)
        - North Church of St. Johnsbury Street, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 189)
        - O'Brien, H., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 190)
        - Orange Judd and Co., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 191)
        - Parker, Emma, 1886-1890 (Box 4, Folder 192)
        - Parker, Rev. Joseph, 1881-1887, undated (Box 4, Folder 193)
        - Paulding, E. P. H., 1876-1878 (Box 4, Folder 194)
        - Perkins, Mary Foote (Beecher), 1860 (Box 4, Folder 195)
        - Plymouth Church, Brooklyn, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 196)
        - Pond, James Burton (1838-1903), 1877-1884 (Box 4, Folder 197)
        - Porter, John K., 1875-1876 (Box 4, Folder 198)
        - Porter, Rose, 1868 (Box 4, Folder 199)
        - Price, J. D., 1888 (Box 4, Folder 200)
        - Raymond, Sarah Mellen (Dwight), 1875 (Box 4, Folder 201)
        - Robbins, T. T., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 202)
        - Rugby Baptist Church, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 203)
        - Sanford, Lucy E., 1869 (Box 4, Folder 204)
        - Scoville, Annie Beecher, 1879-1890 (Box 4, Folder 205)
        - Scoville, Harriet Eliza (Beecher), 1859 April-November (Box 4, Folder 206-207)
        - Scoville, Harriet E. (Beecher), 1859 December-1861 May (Box 4, Folder 208)
        - Scoville, Harriet Eliza (Beecher), 1866-1874, 1882-1891 (Box 4, Folder 209-211)
        - Scoville, Harriet E. (Beecher), 1893-1894, undated (Box 4, Folder 212)
        - Scoville, Rev. Samuel, 1864-1895 (Box 5, Folder 213-214)
        - Scoville, Rev. Samuel (fragment), undated (Box 5, Folder 215)
        - Second Presbyterian Church, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 216)
        - Shirley, D. L., 1875 (Box 5, Folder 217)
        - Shirely, L. D., 1875 (Box 5, Folder 218)
        - Shreve, Alice, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 219)
        - Southwick, John A., 1875 (Box 5, Folder 220)
        - Stannard, Rev. John Turner, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 221)
        - Stowe, Eliza Tyler, (1836-1912), 1859-1895 (Box 5, Folder 222)
        - Stowe, Harriet Elizabeth (Beecher) (1811-1896), 1837-1860, 1866-1874, undated (Box 5, Folder 223-224)
        - Sullivan, Algernon S., 1874 (Box 5, Folder 225)
        - Taft, Julia M, 1874 (Box 5, Folder 226)
        - Taylor, John W., 1874 (Box 5, Folder 227)
        - Terry, Dame Ellen, (1848-1928), 1887, undated (Box 5, Folder 228)
        - Terry, S. B., 1896 (Box 5, Folder 229)
        - Throop, C. G., [1869] (Box 5, Folder 230)
        - T.S. Arthur and Sons, 1869 (Box 5, Folder 231)
        - Unthank, T. C., 1896 (Box 5, Folder 232)
        - Verdi, T. S., 1869 (Box 5, Folder 233)
        - Viccars, Thomas, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 234)
        - Wager, Mary A. E., 1871 (Box 5, Folder 235)
        - Whitelaw, R. M., 1879 (Box 5, Folder 236)
        - Zaraphomithes, A.D. and wife, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 237)
        - Resolution from Ministers of Glasgow, Scotland, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 238)
        - Anonymous, 1876 (Box 5, Folder 239)
      - From E. W. B.:
        - Beach, Chloe Buckingham, 1859-1874, 1876-1889 (Box 5, Folder 240-249)
        - Beach, Chloe Buckingham, undated (Box 6, Folder 250-256)
        - Beach, Ella, 1868 (Box 6, Folder 257)
        - Beach, Emma, 1868 (Box 6, Folder 258)
        - Beach, Moses Sperry (1822-1882), 1863-1872 (Box 6, Folder 259)
        - Beecher family (Box 6, Folder 260)
          See: Boxes 1-2, Folders 54, 74-75
        - Beecher, H. W. (Box 6, Folder 261)
        - Bok, Edward William (1863-1930), 1888 (Box 6, Folder 262)
        - Bullard family members, 1861 (Box 6, Folder 262a)
          See: Box 17, Folder 670
        - Gunn, Frederick William (1816-1881), 1861,1863-1864 (Box 6, Folder 263)
        - Hosford, T. J., Oct, 1869 (Box 6, Folder 264)
        - Howard, Susan Taylor (Raymond), 1872-1873 (Box 6, Folder 265)
        - Ney, Bertha B. Add 8/30/82, 1895 July 1 (Box 6, Folder 265a)
        - Norton, H., undated (Box 6, Folder 266)
        - Robinson, Charles, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 267)
        - Scoville, Annie B. (Box 6, Folder 268)
          See: Box 21, Folder 827
        - Scoville, Harriet E. B. (Box 6, Folder 269)
          See: Box 35, Folders 1575-1584
        - Scoville, Rev. Samuel. (Box 6, Folder 270)
          See: Box 40, Folders 1772-1777
        - Stone, Mrs., 1874 (Box 6, Folder 271)
        - Turner, Thomas J., 1872 (Box 6, Folder 272)
        - Fragments (Box 6, Folder 273)
        - Magazine - Correspondence, 1869 (Box 6, Folder 274)
          See also: Box 98
    - Beecher, Henry Ward
      - To and From:
        - Abbot, Gorham Dummer (1807-1874), 1869 (Box 7, Folder 275)
        - Abbott, Rev. Edward (b. 1841), 1875 (Box 7, Folder 276)
        - Abbott, Rev. Lyman (1835-1922), 1865-1885 (Box 7, Folder 277)
        - Adams, Julius Walker (1812-), 1883 (Box 7, Folder 278)
        - Aiken. Rev. Silas, 1847 (Box 7, Folder 279)
        - Allon, Rev. Henry (1818-1892), 1863-1886 (Box 7, Folder 280)
        - Anderson, Robert (Brig.-Gen) (1805-1871), 1861 (Box 7, Folder 281)
        - Armitage, Rev. Thomas (1819-1896), 1876 (Box 7, Folder 282)
        - Arnold, Isaac Newton (1813-1884), 1883 (Box 7, Folder 283)
        - Arnold, Samuel George (1806-1891), 1875 (Box 7, Folder 284)
        - Arthur, Chester Alan (Pres.) (1830-1886), 1880 (Box 7, Folder 285)
        - Atwood, Rev. Isaac Morgan (1838-1917), 1873 (Box 7, Folder 286)
        - Abbott - Anderson, 1873-1884 (Box 7, Folder 287)
        - Andersen - Atwater, 1874-1883 (Box 7, Folder 288)
        - Bacon, Rev. George Blagden (1836-1876), 1874-1875 (Box 7, Folder 289)
        - Bacon, Rev. Leonard (1802-1881), 1852-1876 (Box 7, Folder 290)
        - Bancroft, Hubert Howe (1832-1918), 1882 (Box 7, Folder 291)
        - Bangor (Maine) Theological Seminary Rhetorical Society, 1876 (Box 7, Folder 292)
        - Barney, Hiram, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 293)
        - Barnum, Phineas Taylor (1810-1891), 1874 (Box 7, Folder 294)
        - Barrows, Rev. John Henry (1847-1902), 1875 (Box 7, Folder 295)
        - Bartlett, Rev. Edward O., 1875-1876 (Box 7, Folder 296)
        - Bartol, Rev. Cyrus Augustus (1813-1900), 1871 (Box 7, Folder 297)
        - Barton, Ira M., 1842-1850 (Box 7, Folder 298)
        - Beach, Charles, 1872-1876 (Box 7, Folder 299)
        - Beach, Chloe Buckingham, 1878-1886, undated (Box 7, Folder 300)
        - Beach, Emma, 1878-1885 (Box 7, Folder 301)
        - Beach, Moses Sperry (1822-1892), 1868-1883 (Box 7, Folder 302)
        - Beach, Violet, 1877-1886 (Box 7, Folder 303)
        - Beecher, Catherine Esther (1800-1878), 1860-1876 (Box 7, Folder 304)
        - Beecher, Charles (1815-1900), 1855-1887 (Box 7, Folder 305)
        - Beecher, Charles McCulloch, 1881 (Box 7, Folder 306)
        - Beecher, Edward (1803-1895), 1829-1875 (Box 7, Folder 307)
        - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard) (1813-1897), 1834-1862 (Box 7, Folder 308-314)
        - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard), 1873-1874, 1876-1879 May, July 1879-July 1884, October 1884-1886, undated (Box 8, Folder 315-321)
        - Beecher, George (1807-1843), 1825-1838 (Box 8, Folder 322)
        - Beecher, George Buckingham (1841-1925), 1863-1873 (Box 8, Folder 323)
        - Beecher, Henry Barton (1841-, 1861-1877, undated (Box 8, Folder 324)
        - Beecher, Henry Barton [extract of a letter], [1864?] (Box 8, Folder 325)
        - Beecher, Herbert Foote (1854-1925), 1871 1873, undated (Box 8, Folder 326)
        - Beecher, Herbert Foote (Fragment) (Box 8, Folder 327)
        - Beecher, Rev. James Chaplin (1828-1886), 1861-1874 (Box 8, Folder 328)
        - Beecher, Rev. Lyman (1775-1863), 1842-1855 (Box 8, Folder 329)
        - Beecher, Mary Eunice (Box 8, Folder 330)
        - Beecher, Rev. Thomas Kinnicut, 1848-1862, undated (Box 8, Folder 331)
        - Beecher, William Constantine (1849-1928), 1863-1878, undated (Box 8, Folder 332)
        - Beecher, Jessie Howe (Bigelow), 1886 (Box 8, Folder 333)
        - Beecher, Rev. William Henry (1802-1889), 1832-1877, undated (Box 8, Folder 335)
        - Beecher's children, undated (Box 8, Folder 336)
        - Beecher's family members circular letters, 1840-1842 (Box 99, Folder 1)
        - Number not assigned (Box 8, Folder 337)
        - Behrends, Rev. Adolphus Julius Frederick (1839-1900), 1879 (Box 8, Folder 338)
        - Bolton, Charles Edward (1841-, 1874 (Box 8, Folder 339)
        - Bonner, Robert (1824-1899), 1858-1874, undated (Box 8, Folder 340-343)
        - Boucicault, Dion (1822?-1890) (Box 9, Folder 344)
        - Bowen, Henry Chandler (1813-1896), 1847-1870 (Box 9, Folder 345)
        - Brace, Rev. Jonathan (1810-1877), 1857 (Box 9, Folder 346)
        - Bradford, Rev. Amory Howe (1846-1911), 1874-1882 (Box 9, Folder 347)
        - Brainerd, Rev. Thomas (1804-1866), 1852 (Box 9, Folder 348)
        - Brooklyn, 1884 (Box 9, Folder 349)
        - Budington, Rev. William Ives (1815-1879), 1863-1874 (Box 9, Folder 350)
        - Bullard, Asa (1804-1888), 1876 (Box 9, Folder 351)
        - Bullard, Lucy, 1838-1856 (Box 9, Folder 352)
        - Bullard, Rev. Oliver Crosby, 1851, undated (Box 9, Folder 353)
        - Bullard, Talbut, 1859 (Box 9, Folder 354)
        - Burdette, Robert Jones ("Bob") (1844-1914), 1882 (Box 9, Folder 355)
        - Butler, Benjamin F., 1852 (Box 9, Folder 356)
        - Bailey - Batchelor, 1852-1878 (Box 9, Folder 357)
        - Bates - Berlin, 1852-1885 (Box 9, Folder 358)
        - Bernard - Bogue, 1863-1884 (Box 9, Folder 359)
        - Bolles - Bruce, 1863-1884 (Box 9, Folder 360)
        - Brunskill - Byewater, 1863-1885 (Box 9, Folder 361)
        - Carr, James, 1877 (Box 9, Folder 362)
        - Channing, William Henry, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 362)
        - Chase, Salmon Portland (1808-1873), 1863 (Box 9, Folder 363)
        - Chesson, F. W., 1863 (Box 9, Folder 364)
        - City Temple, London, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 365)
        - Claflin, Mary B., 1872-1883, undated (Box 9, Folder 366)
        - Clarke, Mrs. Enos, 1879 (Box 9, Folder 367)
        - Cleveland, Grover (Pres.), 1885-1887 (Box 9, Folder 368)
        - Cleveland, Henry Whitney, 1873-1875 (Box 9, Folder 369)
        - Cleveland, 1884 (Box 9, Folder 370)
        - Coffin, Charles Fisher (1823-1916), undated (Box 9, Folder 371)
        - Congregational Union of England and Wales, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 372)
        - Congregational Pastors Union of Chicago and Vicinity, 1873 (Box 9, Folder 373)
        - Curtis, George William (1824-1892), 1884, undated (Box 9, Folder 374)
        - Curwen, Mary T. (Wright), 1867 (Box 9, Folder 375)
        - Cutter, William T., 1846-1874 (Box 9, Folder 376)
        - Cairns - Candee, 1862-1876 (Box 9, Folder 377)
        - Carey - Chase, 1863-1883 (Box 9, Folder 378)
        - Cheever - Clark, 1859-1884 (Box 9, Folder 379)
        - Cleaveland - Cooper, 1868-1884 (Box 9, Folder 380)
        - Copp - Curwen, 1863-1883 (Box 9, Folder 381)
        - Davenport, Amzi Benedict (1817-, 1874 (Box 10, Folder 382)
        - Davis, Noah (1818-1893), 1884 (Box 10, Folder 383)
        - Day, Alice Beecher (Hooker) (1847-1928), 1868 (Box 10, Folder 384)
        - Day, George Edward, 1870 (Box 10, Folder 385)
        - Dean, Rev. Oliver S., 1874 (Box 10, Folder 386)
        - Delano, Columbus (1809-1896), 1869 (Box 10, Folder 387)
        - Derby, James Cephas (1818-1892), 1862-1875 (Box 10, Folder 388)
        - Dexter, Rev. Henry Martyn (Box 10, Folder 389)
        - Dickinson, Anna Elizabeth (1842-1932), 1868-1882 (Box 10, Folder 390)
        - Dixon, M. F., 1870 (Box 10, Folder 391)
        - Dixon, Rev. William T., 1883 (Box 10, Folder 392)
        - Dodge, Mary Abigail (1833-1896) ("Gail Hamilton"), 1869 (Box 10, Folder 393)
        - Dow, Neal, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 394)
        - Drury, Emily (Merwine) [copies], 1855-1863 (Box 10, Folder 395)
          Note: Many of these letters are copies of Manuscripts belonging to the Schlesinger Library, Radcliffe College.
        - Drury, Emily (Merwine), 1864-1886 (Box 10, Folder 396)
        - Duncan, C. C., 1863-1867 (Box 10, Folder 397)
        - Dwight, Timothy (1828-1916), 1875-1877 (Box 10, Folder 398)
        - Dakin - Day, 1847-1885 (Box 10, Folder 399)
        - Dean - Dilworth, 1866-1882 (Box 10, Folder 400)
        - Dobie - Dwight, 1847-1883 (Box 10, Folder 401)
        - Edmonds, John Worth (1799-1874), 1872 (Box 10, Folder 402)
        - Eddy, Rev. Zachary (1815-1891), 1868 (Box 10, Folder 403)
        - Edward, Prince of Wales, 1861 (Box 10, Folder 404)
        - Estcourt, John, 1863-1864, undated (Box 10, Folder 405)
        - Evarts, William Maxwell (1818-1901), 1875-1877 (Box 10, Folder 406)
        - Everest, Rev. Charles Hall (1837-1908), 1876-1878 (Box 10, Folder 407)
        - Eastman Business College - Everitt, 1845-1886 (Box 10, Folder 408)
        - Farquhar, Arthur B. (1838), 1874 (Box 10, Folder 409)
        - Field, Rev. Henry Martyn (1822-1907), 1870 (Box 10, Folder 410)
        - Field, Kate (1854- ), 1869 (Box 10, Folder 411)
        - First Baptist Church Lewiston, Maine, 1876 (Box 10, Folder 412)
        - Ford, John Bruce, 1868 (Box 10, Folder 413)
        - Fremont, Jessie (Benton) (1824-1902), undated (Box 10, Folder 414)
        - Falconer - Flower, 1872-1885 (Box 10, Folder 415)
        - Follette - Fuller, 1852-1875 (Box 10, Folder 416)
        - Garfield, Lucretia (Rudolph) (1832-1918), 1880 (Box 10, Folder 417)
        - Gladden, Rev. Washington (1836-1918), 1866 (Box 10, Folder 418)
        - Greeley, Horace (1811-1872), 1869 (Box 10, Folder 419)
        - Greene, Rev. Richard Gleason (1829- ), 1876 (Box 10, Folder 420)
        - Greey, Edward (1835-1888), 1885 (Box 10, Folder 421)
        - Grinnell, Josiah Buckingham (1821-1891), 1883-1884 (Box 10, Folder 422)
        - Gunn, Frederick William (1816-1881), 1860-1881, undated (Box 10, Folder 423)
        - Gallagher - Gould, 1863-1883 (Box 10, Folder 424)
        - Grant - Guyton, 1863-1885 (Box 10, Folder 425)
        - Hague, James Duncan (1836-1908), 1874 (Box 11, Folder 426)
        - Hale, David (1791-1849), 1847 (Box 11, Folder 427)
        - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909), 1875 (Box 11, Folder 428)
        - Halliday, Samuel Byram (1812-1897), 1874-1884, undated (Box 11, Folder 429)
        - Hanks, Rev. Stedman Wright (1811-1889), 1851-1876 (Box 11, Folder 430)
        - Hawley, Harriet W., 1872 (Box 11, Folder 431)
        - Henry, C. C. [letter with part of a H.W.B. Sermon on verso], 1882 (Box 11, Folder 432)
        - Hewit, Nathaniel (1788-1867), 1853 (Box 11, Folder 433)
        - Hitchcock, Edward (1854-, 1875-1876 (Box 11, Folder 434)
        - Holcombe, James Philemon (1820-1873), 1865 (Box 11, Folder 435)
        - Holley Springs (Miss.), 1884 (Box 11, Folder 436)
        - Hooker, Isabella Beecher (1822-1907), 1872 (Box 11, Folder 437)
        - Hooker, John (1816-1901), 1852-1868 (Box 11, Folder 438)
        - Hope, James Barron (1827-1887), 1868 (Box 11, Folder 439)
        - [Hovey, Edmund Otis] [1801-1877], 1840 (Box 11, Folder 440)
        - Howard, John Raymond (1837-1926), 1868-1882 (Box 11, Folder 441)
        - Howard, John Raymond (1837-1926), 1884-1885 (Box 11, Folder 442)
        - Howard, John Tasker (d. 1888), 1860-1879 (Box 11, Folder 443)
        - Howard, Gen. Oliver Otis (1830-1909), 1865 (Box 11, Folder 444)
        - Howard, Gen. Oliver Otis (Box 11, Folder 445)
          see: box 11, folder 467 box 45, folder 1959
        - Howard, Susan Taylor (Raymond) (d. 1906), 1863-1883 (Box 11, Folder 446)
        - Howe, James Lewis (1859-, 1885 (Box 11, Folder 447)